I'm very hungry, I'm going to eat some cereals.
Are you ok?
Yes, I'm good.
Oh no, the cereals!
We have to clean these cows before our parents arrive.
Yes, but how?
No worries, with turbo back it's super easy to clean them.
What are you doing in my home?
This doesn't matter.
It has a powerful motor of 8000 watts and can deal with all your pets hair and all the dirt of your house.
And listen, listen, it doesn't make any noise.
Listen, it doesn't make any noise.
Put it in a flash and can be yours for only 9999 euros.
Wow, it's very clean.
And now, get out of my home.
Hello guys.
Hello.
Hello dad.
Shh, I'm normal.
You have been alone for 5 minutes.
I hope nothing has happened.
Thank God he didn't notice.
That's true.